<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></description>
        <link>https://dev.tube</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 05:27:26 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://dev.tube/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Neural Arithmetic Logic Units]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Deepmind released a paper just a few days ago describing a module for neural networks called the Neural Arithmetic Logic Unit (NALU). Although deep neural networks can learn to represent and manipulate numerical information, they don't generalize well outside of the range of numbers encountered during training.  Meaning train it on the numbers 1-10 and it won't be able to count to 11. To improve this ability, the researchers created an architecture that represents numerical quantities as linear activations which are manipulated using primitive arithmetic operators, controlled by learned gates. Its really fascinating stuff, i'll detail how it works in this video. 

Code for this video:
https://github.com/llSourcell/Neural_Arithmetic_Logic_Units

Please Subscribe! And like. And comment. That's what keeps me going. 

Want more education? Connect with me here:
Twitter: https://twitter.com/sirajraval
instagram: https://www.instagram.com/sirajraval
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/sirajology

This video is apart of my Machine Learning Journey course:
https://github.com/llSourcell/Machine_Learning_Journey

More Learning Resources:
https://arxiv.org/abs/1808.00508
https://github.com/search?l=Python&q=nalu&type=Repositories
https://deepmind.com/blog/
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vOppzHpvTiQ&list=PL2-dafEMk2A7YdKv4XfKpfbTH5z6rEEj3

Join us in the Wizards Slack channel:
http://wizards.herokuapp.com/

Sign up for the next course at The School of AI:
https://www.theschool.ai

And please support me on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/user?u=3191693]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/v9E7Wg0dHiU</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/v9E7Wg0dHiU</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 01:33:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Undo All the Things!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[I found a command line interactive interpreter that let me undo lines of Python code that I had just typed and executed. I thought this was the coolest thing! How do you hack undo into other programming environments or create new programming environments with it built in?

Starring fork, LD_PRELOAD, readline, terminal escape sequences, pseudoterminals, online shopping, rectangles and circles, and spaceships!

EVENT:

!!Con 2018

SPEAKER:

Tom Ballinger

PERMISSIONS:

Original video was published with the Creative Commons Attribution license (reuse allowed).

CREDITS:

Original video source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zcg1Ku4YB4g]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/rstLHcY3H9M</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/rstLHcY3H9M</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 01:24:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#DCBerlin18 406 Corti The Curious Case of Android Button DAY1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Nicola Corti, Android Engineer, Yelp Inc.

THE CURIOUS CASE OF ANDROID BUTTON
Intermediate / Design / UI/UX / Talk

We interact with buttons every day to get coffee, order pizza, or start a new Gradle build. They may look simple and straightforward, but they have a fundamental role in our environment: create a sense of power. We all love to feel empowered and we all hate being frustrated by bad design. Your users know this as well, they want to feel immediately rewarded when they interact with your UI, and they will quickly drop your app if they get annoyed. At Yelp, we get tens of millions button clicks a day. At that kind of scale, every pixel matters. We tune every single aspect of our buttons to make them simple and powerful, but adjusting every single shadow cast, click animation, or color layer can be tricky. In this talk, we will provide a deep dive into the Android framework and the Support Library to understand how buttons are rendered.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/6MmzwZMYWoA</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/6MmzwZMYWoA</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 01:29:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#DCBerlin18 403 Pinto Escapabstracting the Map DAY1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Marcel Pinto, Lead Android Developer, HERE Technologies

ABSTRACTING THE MAP
Intermediate / Android Architecture / Talk


A while back my PO came to me and said: “Hey! we've got a new map provider, let’s change it”. Panic mode! At the time I was dealing with a legacy app where the Map implementation was everywhere! Every developer eventually faces situations like this one, but not only that, dealing with maps sometimes can get messy and complex. After years dealing with those issues, with new architecture and pattern concepts we can properly abstract the Map, so when your PO says “Let’s change the full Map” you can just say “no problem, give me a minute!” I will try to solve questions like: “In which layer does the Map implementation goes?” “How can we abstract the map from our business logic?” “How to deal with Map Objects and camera updates?” Among other key concepts that will help you deal with Maps in your Android apps.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/UKKZk5LZtm0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/UKKZk5LZtm0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 01:29:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#DCBerlin18 404 Montiel Hacking Growth Beelinguaapps Journey to a Million Organic Downloads DAY1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[David Montiel, CEO & Founder, Beelinguapp
HACKING GROWTH : BEELINGUAPP'S JOURNEY TO A MILLION ORGANIC DOWNLOADS

Beelinguapp is a language learning app built by a single developer. It has reached 1 million organic downloads, Google Play's Editor's Choice and is the highest rated language learning app with 4.8 stars. In this talk David Montiel will talk about the best practices, android design guidelines, methodologies and tools that he used to get Beelinguapp to its current position, an outstanding place for any startup.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/gJ-aDE5yB1k</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/gJ-aDE5yB1k</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 01:29:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[401 Dorfmann Tarasenko Advanced Model View Intent The Missing Guide DAY1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Hannes Dorfmann, Android Developer, Freeletics
Kostiantyn Tarasenko, Senior Android Developer Intermediate Android Architecture, Freeletics

ADVANCED MODEL-VIEW-INTENT: THE MISSING GUIDE
Intermediate / Android Architecture / Talk

State-focused architectural design patterns such as Model-View-Intent (MVI) have seen a recent surge in popularity. Have you already considered implementing a state machine based approach for your app? Are you afraid how this architecture scales in the real world? Have you ever wondered how to deal with in-app navigation, A/B tests, animations or ultimately how to test and maintain such architecture efficiently? In this talk we start where other introduction talks end. We will share our knowledge and learnings about the state- machine- based architecture we use in our app that is used by millions of users.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/mpfHG-aUgGU</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/mpfHG-aUgGU</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 01:29:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#DCBerlin18 405 Schranz ARTist A Novel Instrumentation Framework for Customizing and Analyzing Apps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Oliver Schranz, Researcher & Ph.D. Student, CISPA, Saarland University

ARTIST - A NOVEL INSTRUMENTATION FRAMEWORK FOR CUSTOMIZING AND ANALYZING APPS
Pro / Open Source and Research / Talk

In this talk, I will give an introduction to a novel instrumentation framework called ARTist, the Android Runtime instrumentation and security toolkit, which allows to arbitrarily modify the code of installed apps. Similar to existing approaches, such as Frida and XPosed, this can be used for modding applications (adding or removing functionality) and app analysis (record traffic, change files, modify databases). However, it does not break the app signature and hence modified applications still receive updates without compromising on security. Additionally, it is capable of modifying not only apps, but also the system server (Package Manager, Activity Manager Service, ...) and application framework classes (everything within framework.jar, ...). I will first outline the basic architecture of ARTist that is built on top of the Android Runtime's (ART) on-device compiler. We will have a look at the underlying design decisions and the deployment options, from regular (rooted) devices to custom ROMs. Then, I will introduce the ARTist SDK that allows developers to easily create own Modules to adapt the functionality of their favorite apps to their needs.
The goal is to make you comfortable with creating own extensions for your installed apps. And finally, it will showcase some interesting Modules for different use cases, such as app reversing and analysis for pentesters and researchers, and app customization and modding for developers and power users. By the end of this session, you will be able to judge which problems ARTist can solve and how to get started with your first Module right away.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/w2FWoaRoQLs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/w2FWoaRoQLs</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 01:29:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[React Meetup @ ZEIT]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[An evening to learn and discuss everything React.
https://zeit.co/react-meetup]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/N-5TNKJ7eB0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/N-5TNKJ7eB0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 01:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interfacing R and Python || Andrew Collier]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[R versus Python for Data Science: the heated battle still rages. But is it really necessary to be partisan on this issue? I don't think so. There are strong arguments in favour of both languages and each clearly has a role to play.

My contention is that the best outcome is a compromise: interfacing the two languages allows one to leverage the strengths of both sides. There are already a few options for such an interface. However, the recently released reticulate package from RStudio kicks this capability up a number of notches. It embeds a Python session in the R environment, exposing a seamless and performant interface.

In this talk I will lay out various reasons to embrace the idea of interfacing R and Python, then show how the reticulate package makes this possible. If you use both R and Python then this can significantly simplify and accelerate your workflow.

EVENT:

PyData Berlin 2018

SPEAKER:

Andrew Collier

PERMISSIONS:

PyData provided Coding Tech with the permission to republish this video.

CREDITS:

PyData: https://pydata.org/berlin2018/schedule/presentation/19/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/SAGkRuS7Chc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/SAGkRuS7Chc</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 01:23:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Build a Reactive Flutter App]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Interested in Flutter, but love RxJava and MVI? Curious about how to structure Flutter apps? If so, join along as we explore how to architect apps using using Dart Streams! We'll cover the basics of Streams, how to beef up their power with RxDart, and how to create a Reactive Application with these patterns.

This talk will cover the Bloc pattern introduced by Google. It's similar to MVI, and helps layer your apps, allowing you to write business logic that works flawlessly across three platforms: iOS, Android, and web.

Come learn a bit more about Flutter and the architecture patterns that can help give your apps a testable, reusable, and cohesive structure!

EVENT:

DCBerlin18

SPEAKER:

Brian Egan

PERMISSIONS:

Original video was published with the Creative Commons Attribution license (reuse allowed).

CREDITS:

Original video source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=As6sFqpIwII]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/n5FMO6G5oI8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/n5FMO6G5oI8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 01:23:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PyTorch Coding Challenge (LIVE)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[PyTorch is a popular deep learning library released by Facebook's AI Research lab. In this video, I'll explain some of its unique features, then use it to solve the Kaggle "Invasive Species Monitoring Challenge". Sometimes, certain species of plants can slowly destroy an ecosystem if left unchecked. We're going to build a ResNet classifier using PyTorch to help detect which plants need to be removed to help the larger ecosystem survive. Get hype! Starts at 2:18 

Code for this video:
https://github.com/llSourcell/Pytorch_Coding_Challenge_LIVE

Please Subscribe! And like. And comment. That's what keeps me going. 

Want more education? Connect with me here:
Twitter: https://twitter.com/sirajraval
instagram: https://www.instagram.com/sirajraval
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/sirajology

This video is apart of my Machine Learning Journey course:
https://github.com/llSourcell/Machine...

More Learning Resources:
https://github.com/pytorch/examples
https://pytorch.org/
https://medium.com/@14prakash/almost-any-image-classification-problem-using-pytorch-i-am-in-love-with-pytorch-26c7aa979ec4
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FloMHMOU5Bs

Join us in the Wizards Slack channel:
http://wizards.herokuapp.com/

Sign up for the next course at The School of AI:
https://www.theschool.ai

And please support me on Patreon:
https://www.patreon.com/user?u=3191693]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/TvwYV0viIQE</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/TvwYV0viIQE</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:32:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CNCF Serverless WG Meeting - 2018-08-09]]></title>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/0eig_lLy0lU</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/0eig_lLy0lU</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:32:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IoT Devices Examples | IoT Applications | Internet of Things Training | Edureka]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[** Edureka IoT Training : https://www.edureka.co/iot-certification-training** 
(IoT Playlist: https://goo.gl/hVG7Cw) 
The “Things” in IoT have been inspiring smart and superior systems across the globe at low power and even at low costs. In short, these IoT devices are laying the foundation for countless futuristic projects like proverbial home automation systems or smart cities. Know the best examples of these devices being implemented in the leading use cases of today’s world and understand what they’re made up of and what you can do to make them more secure.
Subscribe to our channel to get video updates. Hit the subscribe button above. 
#IoT #IoTdevices #IoTtutorial #Things #UseCases #InternetOfThings #iotonlinetraining #Edureka 

-------------------------- 

About our IoT Training 
IoT Certification Training is designed by industry experts to make you a Certified IoT Developer. Edureka IoT training covers: 
Understanding of IoT architecture and IoT Decision Framework 
Configure Raspberry Pi, Understand Sensors, Actuators & get started with python on Raspberry Pi 
Program Sensors (Sense-HAT board), Face Detection and reorganization using OpenCV-Python 
Understand various IoT Networking Protocols which are mainly used to develop communication solutions
Getting started with Cloud and Azure IoT Hub, demonstration of Azure IoT Hub APIs 
Architect an End-to-End Solution using Raspberry Pi, Sense HAT, and Azure 
Perform Data Analytics on the collected sensor data, use prediction algorithms to get useful insights 
IoT challenges, business solutions, research scope and current development, Alexa Voice Bot on Raspberry Pi 

-------------------------- 

Who should go for this IoT Training? 
This IoT Certification Training on Azure is for all the professionals who are passionate about work with IoT devices and want to go ahead and make their career as an IoT Developer. It is best suited for individuals who are: 
Software Developers who are venturing into IoT space 
Solution Architects 
Technical Architects 
Students who seek IoT knowledge 
Business Executives and Managers who want to understand the essentials of IoT 

------------------- 

Why Learn IoT? 
Internet of Things is considered as the next big technology revolution after invention of the Internet. It is supposed to make tremendous impacts on lives and may possibly lead to the betterment of millions of lives throughout the world. According to Cisco, over 50 million devices are expected to be connected to IoT by 2020. 
Healthcare, Logistics, Aviation, Education, Information Technology name any thing and IoT will become an integral part of all these verticals. Internet of Things is believed to bring about the singularity which will ultimately converge into becoming the Internet of Everything. IoT has, therefore, become a leading interest of technologists globally and is perceived to be the NEXT BIG THING in IT industry. Learning IoT will not only provide you a career boost but you will also be able to gain insights on how technology has affected the world and will continue to do so in the coming decades. 

For more information, please write back to us at sales@edureka.co 
Call us at US: +18336900808 (Toll Free) or India: +918861301699 
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/edurekaIN/ 
Twitter: https://twitter.com/edurekain 
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/company/edureka 

Customer Review: 
Michael Harkins, System Architect, Hortonworks says: “The courses are top rate. The best part is live instruction, with playback. But my favorite feature is viewing a previous class. Also, they are always there to answer questions, and prompt when you open an issue if you are having any trouble. Added bonus ~ you get lifetime access to the course you took!!! ~ This is the killer education app... I've taken two courses, and I'm taking two more.”]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/17HMbyNaDjM</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/17HMbyNaDjM</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Storytelling: How Medium Shapes Story]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In this 2013 GDC session, Schell Games' Jesse Schell examines the history of how different mediums have shaped and re-shaped the story, cull out the most useful patterns, uses them to look forward to the mediums we know are coming next, and makes some bold predictions about the shape of stories to come.

Register for GDC: http://ubm.io/2gk5KTU

Join the GDC mailing list: http://www.gdconf.com/subscribe

Follow GDC on Twitter: https://twitter.com/Official_GDC 

GDC talks cover a range of developmental topics including game design, programming, audio, visual arts, business management, production, online games, and much more. We post a fresh GDC video every day.  Subscribe to the channel to stay on top of regular updates, and check out GDC Vault  for thousands of more in-depth talks from our archives.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/BjrO-di22v8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/BjrO-di22v8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:30:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cucumber Pro Demo - Webinar, 9th Aug 2018]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In this webinar, Matt Wynne CEO of Cucumber will show you how you can:

- Publish feature files as gorgeous living documentation direct from source control
- Version those documents, using git branches and Releases
- Collaborate around the feature files using in-line conversations
- Publish test results to Cucumber Pro for extra confidence in the documentation

Finally, we’ll look at how you can bring all this together with release approval - allowing business stakeholders to sign off on the requirements, test cases and test results for each release of your product with a single click.

You should watch if you:

- are already invested in BDD as an organisation and ready to 
- amplify that investment
- want to empower product owners to stay involved in the BDD process from beginning to end
- need an in-house appliance installation of Cucumber Pro to keep your feature files secure
- have the clout to access the necessary infrastructure to set up an appliance: a Linux server/VM, SMTP & LDAP access, firewall configuration etc.

Want to become a Cucumber Pro appliance customer? Read up on our requirements and installation steps here - https://app.cucumber.pro/projects/cucumber-pro/documents/branch/master/features/appliance.md

Just want to take our SaaS app for a spin? Sign up here - https://app.cucumber.pro/signup]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/wNBadMEeoEY</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/wNBadMEeoEY</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:29:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Azure Data Factory visual tools now integrated with GitHub | Azure Friday]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Gaurav Malhotra joins Lara Rubbelke to discuss how you can associate a GitHub repository (public & enterprise) to your Azure Data Factory for collaboration, versioning, source control.

For more information, see:

+ Azure Data Factory Visual tools now support GitHub integration (blog post) https://aka.ms/azfr/462/01
+ Visual authoring in Azure Data Factory - Author with GitHub integration (docs) https://aka.ms/azfr/462/02
+ Azure Data Factory overview https://aka.ms/azfr/462/03
+ Azure Data Factory pricing https://aka.ms/azfr/462/04
+ Azure Data Factory docs https://aka.ms/azfr/462/05
+ Create a free account (Azure) https://aka.ms/azfr/462/free]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/3xgbMpDPXNM</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/3xgbMpDPXNM</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:29:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TWC9: CosmosDB JavaScript SDK Updates, Linux on ASE, Underwater Data Center Webcams, and more]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This week on Channel 9, Christina is back, this time wearing more ironic merch (keep those nerd shirt suggestions coming!), and ready to talk about the latest developer news, including:

* 0:30 [Azure Devs at GopherCon](https://twitter.com/OpenAtMicrosoft/status/1027585301127077890), including a workshop on [Cloud-native Go](https://www.gophercon.com/agenda) and an upcoming [Azure Friday takeover](https://twitter.com/azurefriday/status/1027650725881569281). 

* 0:53 [Microsoft Ignite - now with more code](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/ignite/developer?ocid=AID725708_QSG_BLOG_263164&Aud=DEV) and you can [register for Ignite](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/ignite/developer?ocid=AID725708_QSG_BLOG_263164&Aud=DEV). It runs September 24-28 in Orlando.

* 1:24 [Azure CosmosDB JavaScript SDK 2.0 Public Preview](https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/new-azure-cosmosdb-javascript-sdk-2-0-now-in-public-preview/)

* 2:06 [Linux on Azure App Service Enviornment now Generally Available](https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/linux-on-azure-app-service-environment-now-generally-available/)

* 2:48 [Windows Container Support in Azure App Service Public Preview](https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/announcing-the-public-preview-of-windows-container-support-in-azure-app-service/)
* 3:20 [#FiveThings About CSS](https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/5-Things/Episode-25-Five-Things-About-CSS)

* 3:31 [Defrag Tools: Console Command Favorites](https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/Defrag-Tools/Defrag-Tools-195-Console-Command-Favorites)

* 3:44 [The Xamarin Show: FlexLayout for Xamarin.Forms Explained](https://channel9.msdn.com/Shows/XamarinShow/FlexLayout-for-XamarinForms-Explained)

* 4:00 [VS Code Extensions For the Discerning Developer Palette](https://css-tricks.com/vs-code-extensions-for-the-discerning-developer-palette/)

* 4:20 [Microsoft Underwater Data Center Gets Webcams](https://www.theverge.com/tldr/2018/8/9/17669936/microsoft-undersea-datacenter-webcam) amd you can [watch the stream](ttps://natick.research.microsoft.com/) at the project website. Utterly mesmerizing!

* 4:47 **Christina's Pick of the Week** [Meet the 15-year old World Excel Champion](https://www.cnn.com/2018/08/08/us/microsoft-excel-champion-trnd/index.html)

Don't forget to let me know your favorite VS Code extensions in the comments!

Please leave a comment or email us at twc9@microsoft.com.

Follow @CH9 http://www.twitter.com/ch9
Follow @film_girl http://www.twitter.com/film_girl
 
Create a Free Account (Azure) https://aka.ms/c9-azurefree]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/4vZqmfCZ0M0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/4vZqmfCZ0M0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:29:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#DCBerlin 109 Junginger C++ Cross Platform DAY1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Markus Junginger, CTO, ObjectBox

CROSS PLATFORM APP CORES WITH MODERN C++
Cross-Plattform Development, Talk, Pro

C++ is known for its efficiency, but did you know that modern C++ (C++11 and higher) is also fun to work with? For cross platform development, there’s hardly a better choice when it comes to performance sensitive code. And especially on Android with its VM based architecture, C++ outruns any Java/Kotlin based implementation by far.
Cross-platform development with C++ is not restricted to the mobile world. With the right setup, you can boost your productivity by running your code on the desktop with minimal turnaround times. Basically, there’s no Gradle build you need to wait for.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/--DSP1Geuqk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/--DSP1Geuqk</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:28:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#DCBerlin18 110 Srivastava The A,B and C of Lifecicle Components DAY1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Nishant Srivastava, Sr. Android Engineer, Soundbrenner

THE A, B AND C OF LIFECYCLE COMPONENTS
Intermediate / Android Architecture / Talk

If you've been developing Android applications for a while now, you know the pain of handling the lifecycle just right.It’s a pain-point that has existed since the advent of Android, up until recently when Google released Architecture components. As an Android developer you are bugged by handling activity/fragment lifecycle and flow of data in tandem to the lifecycle changes day in and out. Making your code aware about the lifecycle of the process/activity/fragment makes you more confident as a developer and enables faster development. This session would enable you to understand Lifecycle components (ProcessLifecycleOwner, LifecycleOwner, LifecycleObserver) and how they are leveraged in other architecture components like LiveData and ViewModel. By the end of the session you will be able to build your own custom Lifecycle aware Android apps and libraries.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/2lCrTkwnqu4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/2lCrTkwnqu4</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:28:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#DCBerlin18 106 Egan Build a reactive Flutter App DAY1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Brian Egan, Indie Hacker

BUILD A REACTIVE FLUTTER APP!

Interested in Flutter, but love RxJava and MVI? Curious about how to structure Flutter apps? If so, join along as we explore how to architect apps using using Dart Streams! We'll cover the basics of Streams, how to beef up their power with RxDart, and how to create a Reactive Application with these patterns.
This talk will cover the Bloc pattern introduced by Google. It's similar to MVI, and helps layer your apps, allowing you to write business logic that works flawlessly across three platforms: iOS, Android, and web.
Come learn a bit more about Flutter and the architecture patterns that can help give your apps a testable, reusable, and cohesive structure!]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/As6sFqpIwII</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/As6sFqpIwII</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Aug 2018 01:28:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>