<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></description>
        <link>https://dev.tube</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 04:33:39 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://dev.tube/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Python Django Framework - Full Course for Beginners]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Learn the Python Django framework with this free full course. Django is a high-level Python Web framework that encourages rapid development and clean, pragmatic design.

In this tutorial, we will build a full MVC app using the Django official docs as a guide.

⭐️Contents ⭐️
⌨️(0:00) Part 1
⌨️(25:09) Part 2
⌨️(1:06:49) Part 3
⌨️(1:45:25) Part 4
⌨️(2:26:33) Part 5
⌨️(3:18:00) Part 6

This tutorial was developed by the Clever Programmer. Check out the Clever Programmer YouTube channel for more great tutorials: https://www.youtube.com/c/CleverProgrammer

--

Learn to code for free and get a developer job: https://www.freecodecamp.org

Read hundreds of articles on programming: https://medium.freecodecamp.org

And subscribe for new videos on technology every day: https://youtube.com/subscription_center?add_user=freecodecamp]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/cI3FOYIMSYE</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/cI3FOYIMSYE</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 01:34:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Creating an Arabic Programming Language]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Inspired by Ramsey Nasser’s Arabic programming language Qalb, a functional, Lisp-style language, I created Noor, an Algol-based, imperative Arabic programming language. Arabic is my first language, and I wouldn’t have learned to program had I not moved to the US and learned English. I created Noor with the intention of it being a language for middle schoolers and high schoolers. In this talk I’ll share what I learned about creating an Arabic programming language and how Arabic text really works on your computer.

EVENT:

!!Con 2018

SPEAKER:

Ahmed Abdalla

PERMISSIONS:

Original video was published with the Creative Commons Attribution license (reuse allowed).

CREDITS:

Original video source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eCxqAr7LjW8]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/dkO8cdwf6v8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/dkO8cdwf6v8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 01:27:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AWS Cloud Computing Architecture | AWS Certification | AWS Tutorial For Beginners | Edureka]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This Edureka "AWS Cloud Computing Architecture ” video will introduce you to the nitty-gritties of Architecting a Solution with AWS and also explains the various AWS Design Principles.

Check out our AWS Playlist: https://goo.gl/8qrfKU

PHPZipFile: https://aws.amazon.com/getting-started/tutorials/launch-an-app/

Putty: https://www.putty.org/


Following topics are covered in this session:

1. Cloud and AWS
2. Why Move To Cloud?
3. Design Principles
4. Demo: Architecting Cloud Solution
 

Subscribe to our channel to get video updates. Hit the subscribe button above.

 #AWSTutorial #AWSCloudComputingArchitecture #AWSCertification #AWSTraining #AWSDomains #AWSEC2 #WhatIsAWS? #ContentDeliveryNetwork, #AWSDesignPrinciples Compute, Storage, Database, Data Transfer #Messaging #FreeTier #Flexibility #AWSScalability #CloudComputing #EdgeLocations #Flexibility #AvailabilityZones #IntroductionToAmazonWebServices  #edureka

-----------------------------------------------------------------

How it Works?


1. This is a 5 Weeks Instructor led Online Course, 30 hours of assignment and 20 hours of project work.


2. We have a 24x7 One-on-One LIVE Technical Support to help you with any problems you might face or any clarifications you may require during the course.

3. At the end of the training you will be working on a real time project for which we will provide you a Grade and a Verifiable Certificate!

--------------------------------------------------------------------

About The Course

 
AWS holds 69% of the global market share in the cloud computing market. Irrespective of the size of an organization, everyone has started to adopt the cloud services in one way or the other, and AWS is the major player among the Cloud services industry.

AWS Certification Training from Edureka is designed to provide in depth knowledge about AWS architectural principles and its services.

----------------------------------------------------------------------

What are the objectives of our AWS Architect Certification Training?

 During this AWS Architect Training, you’ll learn:

1. AWS Architecture and different models of Cloud Computing
2. Compute Services: AWS EC2, Auto Scaling and Load Balancing, AWS Lambda, Elastic Beanstalk
3. Storage Services : AWS EBS, AWS S3, AWS Glacier, AWS CloudFront, AWS Snowball, Storage Gateway
4. Database Services: AWS RDS, AWS DynamoDB, ElastiCache, AWS RedShift
5. Security and Identity Services: IAM, KMS
6. Networking Services: Amazon VPC, Route 53, Direct Connect
7. Management Tools: AWS CloudTrail, AWS CloudWatch, CloudFormation, OpsWorks, Trusty Advisor
8. Application Services: SES, SNS, SQS

-----------------------------------------------------------------------

What are the skills that you will be learning with our AWS Architect Certification Training?

 
 On the completion of the AWS Architect Training, learner will be able to:

1. Design and deploy scalable, highly available, and fault tolerant systems on AWS
2. Understand lift and shift of an existing on-premises application to AWS
3. Ingress and egress of data to and from AWS
4. Identify the appropriate AWS service based on data, compute, database, or security requirements
5. Identify the appropriate use of AWS architectural best practices
6. Estimate AWS costs and identifying cost control mechanisms

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Who should go for this AWS Architect Certification Training?

 

This AWS Certification Training is designed for the IT professionals who want to pursue a career in Cloud Computing and become AWS Certified Solutions Architect. Our AWS Architect Certification Training helps you to grab this opportunity and accelerate your career. It is best suited for:

1. Professionals who want Project Experience in migrating and deploying AWS solutions
2. Professionals with IT Infrastructure background
3. Professionals with Virtualisation experience
4. DevOps professionals
5. Professionals with understanding of application, server, and network security and compliance

---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

Cognizant, Dell, KPMG, Hitachi, Wipro, Avanade, Annik Inc., Brillio and over 45,000 MNCs across 185 countries use Power BI

For more information, please write back to us at sales@edureka.co

Call us at US: 1855 818 0063(toll free) or India: +91 90191 17772 


Website: https://www.edureka.co/cloudcomputing

Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/edurekaIN/

Twitter: https://twitter.com/edurekain

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/company/edureka]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/i5SoCF-4beI</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/i5SoCF-4beI</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:32:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Network Service Mesh WG Meeting - 2018-08-03]]></title>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/GdocN_l7ZUA</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/GdocN_l7ZUA</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:31:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[OpenTracing Monthly Call - 2018-08-03]]></title>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/lmtIwjzaUMk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/lmtIwjzaUMk</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:31:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rayman Reinvented]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In this 2013 GDC session, Ubisoft's Anais Dusautois & Christophe Villez offer a behind-the-scenes look at the art-focused process of redesigning Rayman. 

Register for GDC: http://ubm.io/2gk5KTU

Join the GDC mailing list: http://www.gdconf.com/subscribe

Follow GDC on Twitter: https://twitter.com/Official_GDC 

GDC talks cover a range of developmental topics including game design, programming, audio, visual arts, business management, production, online games, and much more. We post a fresh GDC video every day.  Subscribe to the channel to stay on top of regular updates, and check out GDC Vault  for thousands of more in-depth talks from our archives.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/p-8eNkUCvnw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/p-8eNkUCvnw</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:30:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Uber Open Source] Distributing Uber's ML Platform with an Operator Framework -- Mingshi Wang]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[During a June 2018 Open Source Meetup at our Seattle office, senior software engineer Mingshi Wang discusses how we leveraged operator frameworks to scale Michelangelo, our machine learning-as-a-service platform.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/0RVPGULAbYg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/0RVPGULAbYg</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Uber Open Source] Profile Spark Applications at Scale -- Bo Yang]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[During a June 2018 Open Source Meetup at our Seattle office, senior software engineer Bo Yang discusses how Uber's open source JVM Profiler enables us to profile Spark applications at scale across our microservices.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/fCTdbX-mG2I</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/fCTdbX-mG2I</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[[Uber Open Source] LogX: Creating Log Observability in Hadoop Workloads at Uber -- Nan Zhu]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[During a June 2018 Open Source Meetup at our Seattle office, software engineer Nan Zhu discusses how Uber developed LogX, a tool that persists and analyzes logs, to enhance observability in our Hadoop ecosystem.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/o0ZrPZPlq6U</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/o0ZrPZPlq6U</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:28:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[My Journey with PHPUnit on Drupal 7 - The Singapore PHP User Group Meetup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Speaker: Ken Chua

Event Page: https://www.meetup.com/sgphpug/events/252472670/

Produced by Engineers.SG
Recorded by: Michael Cheng

Help us caption & translate this video!

https://amara.org/v/kbSQ/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/8adEoW1TesQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/8adEoW1TesQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:27:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Journey as a Freelance Web Developer - The Singapore PHP User Group Meetup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Speaker: Zion Ng

Event Page: https://www.meetup.com/sgphpug/events/252472670/

Produced by Engineers.SG
Recorded by: Michael Cheng

Help us caption & translate this video!

https://amara.org/v/kbSR/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/dtX5ig-YBSg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/dtX5ig-YBSg</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:27:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Web Animations APIs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Animation is back in the web development tool chest! We know of declarative CSS Animations and Transitions and fully featured JavaScript animation libraries like GreenSock, but there's another option: the Web Animation API! In this talk Rachel Nabors will take you on a magical journey with Alice from Wonderland to show you how this new API is used to run the CSS Animations in your browser and how you can use it to generate and manipulate animations in your project. Colorful, interactive, useful fun for all disciplines.

EVENT:

AmsterdamJS Hot Summer Edition 2018

SPEAKER:

Rachel Nabors

PERMISSIONS:

AmsterdamJS Organizer provided Coding Tech with the permission to republish this video.

CREDITS:

Original video source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PZCgLaOXxFw]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/AGiTmjFHs8M</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/AGiTmjFHs8M</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:23:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WRITING BOTS FOR GITHUB]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[My talk is going to be about Probot — GitHub's framework for creating bots. A bot built with Probot is a NodeJS application that handles GitHub's events. Probot allows us to automate and improve GitHub workflow, extend it with tools that we love as far as we wish.

In my talk, I will show what Probot can do right now and how you can create your own bot.

EVENT:

You Gotta Love Frontend Kyiv 2018

SPEAKER:

Denys Dovhan

PERMISSIONS:

YGLF Conference Organizer provided Coding Tech with the permission to republish this video.

CREDITS:

Original video source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AGY0tgyL9Yo]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/cMenLkK8Ulc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/cMenLkK8Ulc</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:23:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Road To ATS London 2018 - The Service Model Part 2: Transparency and Changing the Narrative]]></title>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/65LG0L7IDkQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/65LG0L7IDkQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 01:22:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Advanced Controls for Xamarin.iOS with Syncfusion | The Xamarin Show]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[This week, James is joined by friend of the show Aaron Melamed, Product Solutions Specialist at Syncfusion. Aaron walks us how Essential Studio for Xamarin enabled developers to take advantage of beautiful controls in their Xamarin.iOS apps. Aaron shows off some of the latest and greatest controls that Syncfusion has to offer including their new Kanban board and Diagram for data visualization.

Xamarin Show viewers can get 20% off the Essential Studio for Xamarin with coupon code: XAMARINSHOW

Show Links:

Syncfusion: Essential Studio for Xamarin: https://www.syncfusion.com/products/xamarin

Find James on Twitter: http://twitter.com/jamesmontemagno 
GitHub: http://github.com/jamesmontemagno
Blog: https://montemagno.com
and his weekly development podcast Merge Conflict: http://www.mergeconflict.fm

Never Miss an Episode: https://twitter.com/thexamarinshow

Useful Links:
Xamarin Developer Center: https://developer.xamarin.com/
Xamarin Blog: http://blog.xamarin.com/
Xamarin and Azure: https://www.xamarin.com/azure
Mobile DevOps: https://www.xamarin.com/mobile-devops
Xamarin University Self-Guided: https://university.xamarin.com/self-guided
Create a Free Account (Azure): https://aka.ms/c9-azurefree]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/ndgkjK33udw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/ndgkjK33udw</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:35:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[HDInsight: Fast Interactive Queries with Hive on LLAP]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Murali Krishnaprasad joins Lara Rubbelke to discuss Interactive Query (also called Hive LLAP, or Low Latency Analytical Processing, or Live Long and Process), which is an Azure HDInsight cluster type. Interactive Query supports in-memory caching, which makes Hive queries super-fast and interactive. See how to use HDInsight Interactive Query to analyze extremely large datasets (~100TB) in common file formats such as ORC and CSV using common BI/SQL tools including Zeppelin notebooks and VS Code.

For more information, see:

+ Use Interactive Query with HDInsight (docs) https://aka.ms/azfr/458/01
+ HDInsight overview https://aka.ms/azfr/458/02
+ HDInsight pricing details https://aka.ms/azfr/458/03
+ Create a free account (Azure) https://aka.ms/azfr/458/free]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/RbBuaiJ8qLM</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/RbBuaiJ8qLM</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:34:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Execute Jars and Python scripts on Azure Databricks using Data Factory]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Gaurav Malhotra joins Lara Rubbelke to discuss how you can operationalize Jars and Python scripts running on Azure Databricks as an activity step in a Data Factory pipeline.

For more information:

+ Transform data by running a Jar activity in Azure Databricks docs https://aka.ms/azfr/459/01
+ Transform data by running a Python activity in Azure Databricks docs https://aka.ms/azfr/459/02
+ Azure Databricks overview https://aka.ms/azfr/459/03
+ Azure Data Factory overview https://aka.ms/azfr/459/04
+ Create a free account (Azure) https://aka.ms/azfr/459/free]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/WTiNiiSN2iQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/WTiNiiSN2iQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:34:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#TBTch9 Tour of the .NET CLR team]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Originally published: November 17, 2004

Jason Zander invited Charles Torre to meet the .NET Common Language Runtime team.

Don't know what this team does? Well, the .NET CLR is at the center of all .NET applications. So, if you're writing .NET apps, you are using this team's work.

Original Channel 9 Post: https://channel9.msdn.com/Blogs/TheChannel9Team/Jason-Zander-Tour-of-the-NET-CLR-team]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/uWJ6SCEf5Hw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/uWJ6SCEf5Hw</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:34:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Azure IoT Inception and Vision]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Sam George, Partner Director for Azure IoT Program Management, tells us all about Azure IoT inception and vision. 

Learn more about Azure IoT: https://aka.ms/iotschool
Create a Free Account (Azure): https://aka.ms/c9-azurefree]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/xdZFn4iBbXE</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/xdZFn4iBbXE</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:34:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Learning Functional Programming | Erlang Solutions Webinar]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Erlang Solutions is joined by respected author, researcher and teacher Simon Thompson who is a Professor of Logic and Computation at the University of Kent.

Here he shares valuable insights into how to learn functional programming, which will be suitable for both beginners and experienced programmers.

WEBINAR LIVE DATE: Wednesday 25 May 2018 | 17:30 CEST / 16:30 BST / 11:30 EDT / 08:30 PDT 

 ——————————————————————— 

SPEAKER CONTACT DETAILS 

SIMON THOMPSON - Simon Thompson shares insights about how to learn functional programming, based on his experience of teaching functional programming in Miranda, Haskell, Erlang and OCaml to beginners and experienced programmers over the last thirty years!

He is a researcher, author and teacher, based at the University of Kent. Simon's research has covered many aspects of functional programming, including verification, tool building and testing for Erlang, Haskell and OCaml. He is a published author on type theory, Haskell and Erlang, and run a MOOC on Erlang for FutureLearn.

Twitter: https://twitter.com/thompson_si

 ——————————————————————— 

 COMPANY CONTACT DETAILS 

 ERLANG SOLUTIONS 
 - Website: https://www.erlang-solutions.com 
 - Twitter: https://www.twitter.com/ErlangSolutions 
 - LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/company/erlan… 
 - GitHub: https://github.com/esl]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/Xatsd3U8boY</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/Xatsd3U8boY</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 01:33:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>