<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></description>
        <link>https://dev.tube</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 11:53:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://dev.tube/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cinematic Games Are Dead! Long Live Cinematic Games!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In this 2015 GDC session, Fiction Control's Matthew Weise explains how clever uses of art, interface and UX can make an experience "cinematic" without ever having a single camera cut, and make players walk away feeling like they visited a movie like it was a place. 

Register for GDC: http://ubm.io/2gk5KTU

Join the GDC mailing list: http://www.gdconf.com/subscribe

Follow GDC on Twitter: https://twitter.com/Official_GDC 

GDC talks cover a range of developmental topics including game design, programming, audio, visual arts, business management, production, online games, and much more. We post a fresh GDC video every day.  Subscribe to the channel to stay on top of regular updates, and check out GDC Vault  for thousands of more in-depth talks from our archives.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/82z_sZRl93M</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/82z_sZRl93M</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:29:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[YOW! Lambda Jam 2018 - Brian McKenna - Teaching functional programming at Atlassian]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[My team works on Atlassian Marketplace, a project which started 10 years ago and uses Scala, Haskell and Nix. The Marketplace code uses concepts such as applicative functors, monad transformers and lenses. People joining the team mostly learned concepts as they needed to, through experimentation and asking questions.

Last year we started hosting functional programming classes for more fundamental and broad understanding. We've been using the Data61 (formerly NICTA) Functional Programming Course with a lot of success. This talk will describe how we teach FP, what we've learned about teaching FP and the challenges we face.

Brian's specialties: Functional programming, Haskell, PureScript, Idris, Agda, Scala, JavaScript, Emacs, Git

For more on YOW! Conference, visit http://www.yowconference.com.au]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/4DNwH6lNo1w</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/4DNwH6lNo1w</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:26:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[YOW! Data 2018 - Gala Camacho - Place Activity During the 2018 Gold Coast Commonwealth Games]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Why do people choose to live in one neighbourhood over another? Every day government makes decisions that can change the way a neighbourhood operates and feels. Understanding the impact that these decisions have is convoluted and hard to measure.

In April, the Gold Coast held the 2018 Commonwealth Games. These events, usually advertised as urban renewal or regeneration projects, have a lasting impact on the neighbourhoods where they take place. Usually, there is a strong push to predic the impact of the games through economic assessments and surveys, however, once the games are happening, is that impact tracked? Sometimes, further economic assessments are produced years after the event which evaluate whether the impact was as expected. Can we do better?

Social data can provide us with more timely evidence of whether the event is activating the economy as expected, or maybe highlight issues that can be resolved.

Using social media data we will explore Facebook places data during and after the games, ultimately generating a dashboard to help us visualise change by giving us the ability to filter and aggregate the data. We will manage the data using Python’s Pandas, generate quick visualisations using Plotly, and finish off by spinning up a dashboard using Plotly’s Dash.

Gala is a mathematician and programmer using data analytics to improve the way we understand cities. With a diverse background in secondary education, volunteering, optimisation and all-things data, Gala is enthusiastic to find solutions to interesting problems and innovative ways to visualise data.

At Neighbourlytics, Gala investigates what information can be extracted from urban data sources to define and visualise the unique local identity of a neighbourhood.

Gala is driven to positively impact her community through her skills and her voice. As such, she is involved with multiple organisations aimed at making the world (but particularly, the tech-world) a better place for women.

For more on YOW! Conference, visit http://www.yowconference.com.au]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/aK70iMtvMuA</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/aK70iMtvMuA</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:26:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ruby After 25 Years by the Creator of Ruby]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Two things are apparent when watching Yukihiro “Matz” Matsumoto, creator of Ruby programming language, talk on the stage. First, that he will do anything he can to enable Ruby to survive and thrive and, second, that he’s thoroughly enjoying himself doing what he does. He’s passionate about Ruby and its community and his outlook is quite simple: Programming is fun, he’s had fun for the last 25 years making Ruby and at the age of 52 now, he hopes that he’ll get to spend the next 25 years having as much fun working on the language he dreamt up and wrote down in – a now lost – notebook, at the age of 17.

EVENT:

Engineering.SG Meetup 2018

SPEAKER:

Yukihiro Matsumoto (Matz), creator of Ruby

PERMISSIONS:

Original video was published with the Creative Commons Attribution license (reuse allowed).

CREDITS:

Original video source: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gTNC26BtRFc]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/jqnVaYUcjCo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/jqnVaYUcjCo</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:26:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JuniorDevSG Developer's Gym with ThoughtWorks (Session 2) - JuniorDevSG]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Speaker: Gordon Guo

Event Page: https://www.meetup.com/Junior-Developers-Singapore/events/252530990/

Produced by Engineers.SG
Recorded by: Michael Cheng

Help us caption & translate this video!

https://amara.org/v/k64T/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/3l_qYu0-fSU</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/3l_qYu0-fSU</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:26:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TechLadies Pre-Bootcamp Workshop 2018 (Session 2) - TechLadies]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Speaker: Sahil Bajaj, ThoughtWorks

Slides: https://www.dropbox.com/s/81t2dj7rngpepkn/techladies%20-%20intro%20to%20js%20and%20react.pdf?dl=0

Instructions: https://github.com/TechLadies/bootcamp-4-technical-task/blob/master/setup-guide.md

Event Page: https://www.eventbrite.sg/e/techladies-bootcamp-4-pre-bootcamp-workshops-tickets-47615313685#

Produced by Engineers.SG
Recorded by: Michael Cheng

Help us caption & translate this video!

https://amara.org/v/k61G/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/NpMZp1bfvlg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/NpMZp1bfvlg</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:26:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TechLadies Pre-Bootcamp Workshop 2018 (Session 3) - TechLadies]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Speaker: Tan Jun Qi, ThoughtWorks

Workshop Material: https://github.com/TechLadies/react-express-mongo-prebootcamp-workshop-3-2018

Event Page: https://www.eventbrite.sg/e/techladies-bootcamp-4-pre-bootcamp-workshops-tickets-47615313685#

Produced by Engineers.SG
Recorded by:

Help us caption & translate this video!

https://amara.org/v/k62f/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/PXVwRNU-z8U</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/PXVwRNU-z8U</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:26:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[JuniorDevSG Developer's Gym (Session 3) - JuniorDevSG]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Speaker: Reuben Tan

Material: https://github.com/CoderKungfu/intro-to-docker-workshop

Event Page: https://www.meetup.com/Junior-Developers-Singapore/events/253082881/

Produced by Engineers.SG
Recorded by: Michael Cheng

Help us caption & translate this video!

https://amara.org/v/k67B/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/kEO4eoQOJns</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/kEO4eoQOJns</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 01:26:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[microPython for ESP32]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Nick Moore
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/202/
Python is small. Micro even.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/-MrqCmq3Z5k</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/-MrqCmq3Z5k</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Running production workloads in a programmable infrastructure]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Alejandro Tesch
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/165/
Infrastructure as Code is a hot topic today, however several IT managers and System Administrators often fail to see the benefits that it can provide to their day to day operations.

In this mini-conf session we will go in depth into two use cases that can leverage on OpenStack to address common operation challenges.

1) We will demo how to leverage HEAT and Ansible to automate the deployment of a two-tier load balanced environment within seconds that will host your enterprise applications.  We will showcase as well the autoscaling capabilities by overloading our web farm until we hit the CPU threshold that will spawn another tomcat server.

2) "Data Cloning as a Service" will demonstrate how to automate the cloning of a 24 x 7 Mission critical Oracle database without impacting the end users.

Ansible is used to place an enterprise database in backup mode, take a snapshot of the volume containing the Database, clone the cinder volume and get it transferred to a development tenant who will automatically start a clone of the database for testing and QA.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/2Gu_rPxuQyQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/2Gu_rPxuQyQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lightweight inventory management with Pallet Jack]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Karl-Johan Karlsson
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/114/
Inventory management for systems administrators is crucial for day-to-day operations. When installing a new machine, its MAC address needs to be registered with the DHCP server. While it runs, the configuration management system needs to know what role it has so it can install the correct software. When it breaks, you need to know which rack and switch port to find it in, its serial number and when its service contract expires.

We present [Pallet Jack](https://github.com/saab-simc-admin/palletjack), a systems administrator-friendly inventory database.

Its back-end store consists of a directory tree with YAML fragments, which means you can insert, version and extract information using standard text processing tools. Inheritance and automatic text processing eliminates the need to store duplicated information. Finally, a simple but powerful Ruby library helps with generating configuration files from the database.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/4oq4ursOnlw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/4oq4ursOnlw</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Sound of Silencing]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Julien Goodwin
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/164/
Having automatic monitoring alerting us when there's problems with our systems
is a core part of ensuring reliable systems, however this can lead to alert
fatigue.

This talk will cover using silencing, grouping and ihibition to reduce alert
load, and improve the signal to noise ratio of remaining alerts.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/9n2K0PnBKys</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/9n2K0PnBKys</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[QA in the Open]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Matthew Treinish
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/156/
One common misconception about a lot of Open Source projects is that the quality is variable and/or is of a secondary concern. This is supported to a certain degree by a lot of projects which do minimal testing upstream and rely on downstream consumers to do more thorough testing. But, there is no reason that an open project can not also do QA in the open as part of the community. While the term QA will likely evoke a plethora of negative emotions from anyone who has worked in a corporate development environment, there can be real benefits to having a dedicated QA effort on an open source project. It enables transparency in how testing is done, lets anyone contribute and collaborate, and can signal to users the stability of a project. This talk will use OpenStack as an case study to explore how an open source project can do QA in an open manner and the potential benefits it can provide.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/ARV1OuBYYUE</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/ARV1OuBYYUE</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Beautiful Build: Releasing Linux Source Correctly]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Bradley M. Kuhn
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/171/
Most embedded computing products run Linux.  However, obtaining the complete, corresponding source code (CCS), which Linux's license (the GNU GPL) requires, can prove difficult.  The license dictates certain technical requirements; verification of a source code release for license compliance therefore requires technical analysis.  After years of reviewing many source releases for embedded Linux products, the speaker discovered (finally!) an excellent example of CCS, which not only meets the requirements of the GPL, but also enables and encourages users to take advantage of their rights to modify and install new versions of the software on their device.

This talk briefly discusses the components of the router's source release, and then explains the aspects of the source release that made it particularly outstanding.  The talk proposes methods to achieve similar compliance successes on embedded products, suggests procedures for increasing the "tinkerer" userbase by improving beyond even what this excellent example provided, and gives insight into and perspective on compliance engineering analysis that occurs during GPL enforcement work.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/C6HDJThJjyw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/C6HDJThJjyw</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Community Leadership Summit Summary]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[VM and group leaders]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/GXITFkxslhU</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/GXITFkxslhU</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Multiplayer gaming and distributed state]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Caskey L. Dickson
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/197/
The hardest thing about writing games (after gamplay, mechanics, ux, marketing and paying the bills) is managing the game state as viewed by all users.  This talk will cover the principles of distributed shared state, strategies such as frequent state regeneration, change validation and how your choice of connectivity and latency profiles change the user experience.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/LQTaknsCI0I</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/LQTaknsCI0I</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Interface citizen scientists with government.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Johan Codinha
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/148/
The victorian biodiversity is facing constant danger, from bush fires to  pest and weeds just to name few. To protect the different ecosystem from natural and human disaster the government needs data !
I am going to walk you thru the history of biodiversity data collection in Victoria ( it's a young country so it's gonna be a short walk ), from hundreds of government employee surveying the countryside in the 80's to 2016 where we rely almost exclusively on citizen scientists to provide accurate data.
Then we will have a look at tools of the past, present and future for collecting biodiversity data and what is the role of standards and open software.
Government agencies are taking land management decision based on biodiversity databases, we will have a look at how the data is beeing verified and what are the potential security risks.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/OXGr4KlQ05E</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/OXGr4KlQ05E</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Opening & Welcome]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Chris Neugebauer / Karen Sandler]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/Sc7NKOCjugo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/Sc7NKOCjugo</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Almost Open - Just close the door behind you]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Steven Ellis
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/147/
We are potentially at an interesting tipping point in the future of Free and Open Source software as more of our interactions are managed by services rather than applications. Does Open Source have a future or are we pivoting towards a services based ecosystem where the best we can hope for is some degree of Open Standards? These open standards have no specific entity tasked with defining each of them, yet every day we hear about Open Hardware, Open Government, Open APIs.

What does Open mean within the ecosystem you operate within, and how can we continue to be a catalyst for the journey and grow the Open Source movement when so many closed outcomes are being produced from the Open Source ecosystem?

This is a collaborative session to look unpack the issue and formulate some actions that can be used by the attendees within their communities, businesses and organisations.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/ceYMBBiVfCE</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/ceYMBBiVfCE</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ESP32 development example using IoTuz]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Andy Gelme
http://linux.conf.au/schedule/presentation/203/
Developing for IoTuz on ESP32 with an example.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/dugl8N6wZSA</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/dugl8N6wZSA</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 01:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>