<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></description>
        <link>https://dev.tube</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 04:28:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://dev.tube/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Yin and Yang of DevOps Transformation - Electric Cloud]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Yin and Yang of DevOps Transformation

Steve Brodie, CEO, Electric Cloud

In Chinese philosophy, Yin and Yang represent seemingly opposing, yet complementary, elements that  must work in harmony to maintain balance and effectiveness. In today’s software economy, DevOps requires traditionally conflicting teams (Dev and Ops) to work in harmony to maintain stability while delivering continuous change. But delving deeper, we discover other significant DevOps dualities that must interact in harmony to form an effective dynamic system. This session will explore these DevOps dualities and elements and highlight ways organizations can empower DevOps teams by providing the necessary mindset, culture and technologies they need to flourish and accelerate the rate of software innovation they deliver to the world.

DOES16 London
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/eur/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/1AfhRPLoQPc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/1AfhRPLoQPc</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A Practical Discussion on Becoming Agile - IBM & Lloyds Banking Group]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Innovate, Learn and Disrupt - A Practical Discussion on Becoming Agile

Sanjeev Sharma, CTO, DevOps Technical Sales and Adoption, IBM Distinguished Engineer, IBM
Mark Howell, Digital DevOps Lead, Lloyds Banking Group

Description:
Digital disruptors are forcing us to rethink the flow of value and how businesses operate. Today, success hinges on an ability to learn and rapidly evolve offerings based on feedback from clients and prospects alike. To achieve this dramatic level of agility, today’s businesses are adopting DevOps to collapse barriers between business leaders, developers and customers, enabling them to rapidly build and market new products, experiment with disruptive innovations, and continuously assess user feedback to align those innovations with expectations and demand. DevOps leads for Lloyds Banking Group, and Monitise PLC, in discussion with Sanjeev Sharma, IBM, will unpack what the “new normal” is for disruptive software delivery. Learn how to assess your own organization’s readiness for DevOps, and to identify the next steps to adopting its practices.

DOES16 London
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/eur/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/45D3mkuzP8s</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/45D3mkuzP8s</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shifting Sand: How a Large DoD Project Moved Toward DevOps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Shifting Sand: How a Large DoD Project Moved Toward DevOps

Jeffery Payne, CEO, Coveros, Inc.
Dan Gahafer, Program Manager (former), DISA forge.mil Program, DISA

DevOps within Federal Agencies can be difficult to achieve when disparate, competing companies are involved in various aspects of a large-scale project. This case study discusses how one such program was successfully moved toward DevOps using value stream analysis and logic. Lessons learned and pitfalls will be discussed as well as metrics used to measure successes. Topics tackled will not only include a discussion of how CI/CD was implemented but how security and compliance was integrated into the process.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/6l7zeU1Le0M</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/6l7zeU1Le0M</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Mainframe DevOps Team Saves the Day at Walmart]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Mainframe DevOps Team Saves the Day at Walmart

Rosalind Radcliffe, Distinguished Engineer, Chief Architect for DevOps, IBM
Rich Jackson, Principal Systems Engineer, Walmart Technology

This session will discuss the success story from Walmart on how they built a set of services on the mainframe to provide capabilities at a large scale for their distributed teams, as well as discuss the transformation required for mainframe teams to achieve this success.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/7Tcv9Jj6QmM</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/7Tcv9Jj6QmM</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Top Technical Talent Programs - Adrian Cockcroft]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Adrian Cockcroft, Formerly with Battery Ventures, Technology Fellow

Adrian recently left Battery Ventures and joined Amazon Web Services as VP Cloud Architecture Strategy, but is not representing AWS in this talk.

In the journey to DevOps many organizations complain that they don't have the right technical talent, and it;s clear that "getting out of the way of innovation" is necessary but not sufficient to hire and retain key people. Compensation and career path are also big factors.
Many large organizations have some kind of Distinguished Engineer or Technical Fellow program, they take many forms, but their primary purpose is to provide a career path to help leverage and retain top technical talent as individual contributors. In this talk we will compare and contrast several example programs, and attempt to answer questions such as, "Should we do this too?", "What unintended consequences might occur?", "How many people should be in the program?", "How does this relate to DevOps?". In my own career I have been a Distinguished Engineer at Sun Microsystems and eBay, and a Technology Fellow at Battery Ventures. I've also reached out to people in similar positions elsewhere to gather more examples.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/CSL-vNQW3SM</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/CSL-vNQW3SM</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Lessons from 50 Enterprise DevOps Transformations - Sendachi]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Mr. Benjamin Wootton, Co-Founder, Sendachi

Over the last few years, we have worked on over 50 DevOps transformations, in many instances with large, global, traditional enterprise organisations. 

During this time, we have gained hard won experience in how to be successful in modernising organisations to DevOps—changing working practices, re-structuring organisations, and re-platforming legacy technology stacks to benefit from infrastructure as code and other DevOps practices. 

In this talk we will talk about our experiences and hard won lessons of how to be successful with a DevOps transformation, with many real world case studies referenced.

DOES16 London
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/eur/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/JdLhnyoNHGk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/JdLhnyoNHGk</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Unilever DevOps Journey So Far: Finding the Speed to Innovate]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Unilever Journey So Far: Finding the Speed to Innovate with DevOps

Kjersten Moody, VP Information & Analytics, Unilever
Sarah Chong, DevOps Evangelist, Unilever

Organisations are quickly discovering that they can test and launch digital products, tools and services faster, and at a lower cost by integrating their development and IT operations teams. This process has become a competitive advantage for many and Unilever has been working on capturing its full value potential. 

In this short keynote speech Kjersten Moody, VP Information & Analytics and Sarah Chong, DevOps Evangelist will discuss the need to emphasize the sharing of information and processes across product-development and IT operations groups to enable the frequent release of small internal updates, alongside appropriate tooling and metrics for success. They will talk about how the journey started at Unilever, the change in culture required to have impact, success stories and what next with DevOps.

DOES16 London
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/eur/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/MbAZkkOwXl4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/MbAZkkOwXl4</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DevOps at Ordnance Survey: Turning the Dinosaur Into a Unicorn - Simon Parkes]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[DevOps at Ordnance Survey – Turning the Dinosaur Into a Unicorn

Simon Parkes, Enterprise Infrastructure Architect, Ordnance Survey

Description:
This talk will demonstrate how a government organisation with 225 of history, specialist software systems comprised of monolithic COTS applications, and a large number of manual update and maintenance processes, adopted DevOps across the enterprise to create agility, fast delivery cycles and huge efficiencies with project delivery cycles.

DOES16 London
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/eur/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/_fQJvo5Xy10</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/_fQJvo5Xy10</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuous Delivery in a Primeval Environment - Thomas Cook]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous Delivery in a Primeval Environment

Lee Sexton, Head of DevOps, Thomas Cook

Working the minds and souls of monolithic business, bringing new ways of working to a multitude of cultures and breaking the silos inside a silo.

DOES16 London
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/eur/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/inyXz8DA_Y8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/inyXz8DA_Y8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Commonalities of Agile & DevOps Transformation for Conservative Organizations]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Commonalities of Agile and DevOps Transformation for Large Conservative Organizations: Horses with dreams of becoming Unicorns

Mrs. Robin Yeman, Agile / DevOps Coach, Lockheed Martin
Suzette Johnson, Northrop Grumman Fellow Agile / DevOps Coach, Northrop Grumman

In this presentation we look at the commonalities that we have experienced in our DevOps journey. While working for two large companies and helping teams implement a DevOps mindset we discovered similar approaches and techniques. From growing the team and the skills needed for this transition to looking at the larger organization as system in need of streamlining processes, we will share practices that have worked well for these teams and how to begin building a DevOps culture.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/m5O9V6yz5FI</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/m5O9V6yz5FI</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Communication Between Tribes: A Story of Silos, DevOps and Government]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Communication Between Tribes: A Story of Silos, DevOps and Government

Gareth Rushgrove, Senior Software Engineer, Puppet; previously UK GDS

In any large organisation silos exist, protective of their domain and particular specialism. DevOps conversations often turn to how to break down those silos, to encourage multidisciplinary working and move from thinking about the requirements of the IT department or the security group to thinking about the needs of end users.

This talk, based on my experience working across the UK Government as an early member of the Government Digital Service, will discuss:

-How being able to speak the language of a specific discipline, be it information security or service management or software development, is the first step to breaking down barriers
-The importance of understanding stereotypes (including of yourself) when it comes to communicating across silos
-The problems caused when policy documentation becomes separated from the owner of that policy
-The usefulness of software as a shared interface to a shared problem

It’s often too easy when talking about silos to believe the answer is for one side to give in, for DevOps to succeed that you have to allow the IT group and the software group to fight until only one remains.

This talk will hopefully talk about a better way forward.

DOES16 London
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/eur/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/sK4Z618ZDQ4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/sK4Z618ZDQ4</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Starbucks Technology Transformation - Courtney Kissler]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Starbucks Technology Transformation

Courtney Kissler, Vice President of Retail Technology, Starbucks

Courtney is the Vice President of Retail Technology at Starbucks. She’s accountable for the global POS and retail store technology experiences. Prior to Starbucks, Courtney spent 14 years at Nordstrom with her last role being the Vice President of E-Commerce and Store technologies where she drove a technological transformation essential for outpacing the demands of today’s Omnichannel consumers. She was accountable for program management, delivery, and support for all customer facing technologies including in-store, Web, and mobile touch points. Courtney joined Nordstrom as a security engineer in 2002 and held a variety of leadership roles across the technology organization. Courtney is a graduate of Eastern Washington University with a B.S. in Computer Information Systems and worked at two startups, CyberSafe and WorldStream Communications, prior to joining Nordstrom.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/uImY8iWYWu8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/uImY8iWYWu8</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DevOps Transformation, Driving Culture Change - HPE]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[DevOps Transformation, Driving Culture Change

Ruly Weisbach, Director of R&D, HPE

DOES17 London
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/eur/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/3-_gx3KLlIo</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/3-_gx3KLlIo</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:31:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Inside-Out of Creating a DevOps Movement - Bluware Inc]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Inside-Out of Creating a DevOps Movement

Eddie Garcia, DevOps Practice Manager, Bluware Inc

You don't always have the luxury of a top down DevOps initiative, what is a non-conforming DevOps minded individual to do? Become a DevOps guerrilla and start a grassroots DevOps movement. The presentation will center around two cases Microsoft:Mac Office and a major Oil and Gas R&D department. In both of these situations there was resistance and non-technical obstacles to overcome and in the end change was brought from the bottom up. What is offered are techniques to use to build consensus and momentum for your very own grassroots DevOps movement.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/1GcFu5xzscc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/1GcFu5xzscc</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:30:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tactics for Influencing Executives and Middle Management - Leading Change]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/49J__6GLy38</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/49J__6GLy38</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:30:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Compliance Help for the Agile Enterprise - Adobe]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Compliance Help for the Agile Enterprise

David Owczarek, Sr. Manager, Cloud Technology, Adobe Systems Incorporated

Implementing controls for SOCII, PCI-DSS, HIPPA and other compliance standards is complex, detail-oriented work. Doing that in an enterprise with agile teams makes it even harder. This talk offers several conceptual frameworks for implementing agile controls. By looking at each control from four different perspectives: code, process, infrastructure, and evidence, concrete requirements for the solution rapidly emerge. Controls are also grouped by their frequency – continuous or periodic. Periodic controls are used to examine the consumption of people’s time in a 12 month, forward-looking view. Finally, three hard truths about compliance work provide an emotional framework.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/5Fqo7MLSpnI</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/5Fqo7MLSpnI</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:30:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DevOps at New Zealand Ministry of Social Development - David Habershon]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[DevOps at New Zealand Ministry of Social Development

David Habershon, Chief Information Officer at Ministry of Social Development, New Zealand

This is an experience story about a government organization learning to run very fast with a new DevOps program. It's a very large organization dealing with human services. The MSD has the third largest IT department in New Zealand.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/7B4auX_xME0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/7B4auX_xME0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:30:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Continuous Monitoring in DevOps for Large Health Care - UHG/Optum]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Continuous Monitoring in DevOps for Large Health Care

Professor Phil Lerner, Distinguished Engineer, UHG/Optum

Security has become a stakeholder in the new DevOps as a rugged partner to the teams. As we evaluate new tools, their interconnectivity, isolation, sandbox and enablement for the DevOps community we have developed a conceptual security architecture that would allow DevOps to move at the rapid delivery pace they are used to while security will become a transparent set of controls and part of the fabric or control plane of the tools suites we choose to enable to transform the DevOps experience. This presentation will cover those advanced technical topics with a strong focus on cyber security in DevOps.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/9zsXQqIPoVE</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/9zsXQqIPoVE</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:30:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[When IT Closes the Deal - Equifax]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[When IT Closes the Deal

Brandon Holcomb, VP Technology, Global Platforms at Equifax, Equifax Inc.
Andy Cooper, SVP, Technology, Global Platform Services, Equifax Inc.

Description:
Equifax powers the financial future of individuals and organizations around the world. Using the combined strength of unique trusted data, technology and innovative analytics, Equifax has grown from a consumer credit company into a leading provider of insights and knowledge that helps its customers make informed decisions.

Delivering on that trust requires both business and technical operations excellence. Faced with the growing challenges of the modern marketplace, the Equifax IT organization embarked on a top-to-bottom cultural and technical transformation. This presentation will outline how the Equifax IT team has taken steps towards transforming itself into a nimble, efficient and internally-capable organization. Topics will include key management lessons learned, budget realignment, creating partnerships across organizational boundaries and strategic projects to focus the organization’s transformation efforts. The early results? IT is no longer viewed as a liability to the business, instead IT is now an asset – a strategic partner that is actively helping to close deals.

DOES16 San Francisco
DevOps Enterprise Summit
https://events.itrevolution.com/us/]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/PdJkny2HVVQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/PdJkny2HVVQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:30:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Adopting DevOps @ Scale: Lessons Learned at NBCUniversal, Kaiser Permanente, GitHub and IBM]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Adopting DevOps @ Scale: Lessons Learned at NBCUniversal, Kaiser Permanente, GitHub and IBM

Sanjeev Sharma, CTO, DevOps Technical Evangelist, IBM Distinguished Engineer, IBM
John Comas, Manager of Platform DevOps, NBCUniversal
Raghunath Raman, Director, Digital APIs & Integration Delivery, Kaiser Permanente
Aziz Shamin, Solutions Engineering Manager, GitHub

IBM Sponsor Track talk: 
DevOps is evolving into a major enabler of business innovation. Done well it can drive digital transformation at an enterprise level. But crossing the chasm from successful DevOps pilots with two-pizza teams to enterprise adoption remains a challenge. Join DevOps for Dummies author Sanjeev Sharma as he hosts a discussion with DevOps pros from enterprises that are successfully achieving scale as they unpack the "new normal" for disruptive software delivery. NBCUniversal is accelerating creativity and engineering effectiveness while improving collaboration and connectivity with increased security. Kaiser Permanente is managing the cultural, process and technology challenges of multi-speed IT. GitHub builds software that millions of developers and thousands of businesses use to collaborate on code and build better software, faster. And IBM has embarked on a DevOps transformation that has engaged over 10,000 developers already -- and in the process become one of the world's largest users of GitHub Enterprise. You'll learn how to assess your own organization’s readiness for scaling DevOps, and to identify next steps. Please join us!

www.itrevolution.net
DevOps Enterprise Summit San Francisco 2016]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/TmAY9iqKKnM</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/TmAY9iqKKnM</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 01:30:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>