<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></description>
        <link>https://dev.tube</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 04:30:32 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://dev.tube/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 48]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the Code: http://goo.gl/bwVX8

I show you how to Make a Java Paint Application! One of you guys asked me to do this and it gives me a great opportunity to review and cover new topics all at once.

I cover swing, events, mouse events, Graphics2D, ArrayList, and numerous other topics.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/235mse79MCw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/235mse79MCw</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 50]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the Code: http://goo.gl/Kt95u

I wanted to make the 50th part of my Java Video Tutorial special! In this tutorial, I answer numerous questions.

I begin showing you how to design a game like Asteroids. I start teaching OOP design principles using UML. You learn how to draw polygons on the screen and how to animate them. And, to top it all off I show you how collision detection works.

Yes, there is a lot in this 14 minute video :)]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/4wWLEeQSXLQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/4wWLEeQSXLQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 60]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the game: http://goo.gl/LWesG

In this video I continue my Java Asteroids game. I pretty much finish up the game in this tutorial.

I show you how to do a bunch of new things. I show you how to play sound in a JFrame. We introduce yet another way to handle collision detection. We remove items from the screen when they are destroyed. And, a whole bunch more is covered.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/8A3ziZPZbgQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/8A3ziZPZbgQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 54 Java Polygon Collision Detection]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get Everything Here: http://goo.gl/JmTrs

I've been asked many times to create a program that handles Java collision detection with polygons. This is a continuation of my tutorial on how to make a Java video game and if you haven't been watching you should check it out.

It is surprisingly easy to handle collision detection with polygons. All you have to do is surround all of your polygons with rectangles and a handy dandy method named intersects handles pretty much everything else!]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/8KNwjOsdn8I</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/8KNwjOsdn8I</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Eclipse Shortcut Keys]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the Cheat Sheet: http://goo.gl/OI9DU

I have been asked many times to cover the Eclipse shortcut keys that I use all of the time, so in this tutorial I will do just that. I did my best to limit the tutorial to the most commonly used shortcuts I use so that they are easier to memorize. I also provide them in a table below.

Both the Auto Complete and the Keystroke shortcuts are covered. I hope this helps you write code quicker. Feel free to leave your own favorites in the comment section below if you think I missed something important.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/C5glFtpuy0U</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/C5glFtpuy0U</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 58]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get all the code: http://goo.gl/J3MtJ

As we continue to make an asteroid Java game, I show you how to make your space ship shoot.

It sounds like a simple concept until you realize the ship is shooting while it is rotating through space at an angle that may not be equal to the direction it is moving. Don't worry, we'll figure it out together in this and the next tutorial.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/MfqbEYyg3J8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/MfqbEYyg3J8</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 57]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the code: http://goo.gl/5I88E

In this video I continue making a Java Asteroids game while teaching about OOP design principles. In previous videos I showed how to make a Java UML class diagram and then we turned the UML class diagram into a class.

Here I finish up the class so that you can now fly your ship in any direction. You'll also be able to keep it on the game board and use life like velocity that accelerates.

All of the code is  heavily commented to help you learn.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/S1xCzB4d9G8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/S1xCzB4d9G8</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 49]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the Code: http://goo.gl/zuTwv

In this part of my Java Video Tutorial, I continue to show you how to make a Java paint application. If you missed part 1 watch it.

I cover numerous topics including: how to draw lines, ellipses, brush strokes. I also cover how to save transparency values for shapes. And, because you requested it how to create a custom event listener and much more.

After this tutorial, you'll be able to make an app with much of the functionality of Photoshop.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/T6FxSiYQ7nI</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/T6FxSiYQ7nI</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 56]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the finished code: http://goo.gl/sCL6A

In this part of my Java video tutorial I turn the SpaceShip UML class diagram I designed in the last video into a real class.
 This class will allow you to fly the space ship around the screen at any angle. You'll be able to rotate it while maintaining the ships current direction. It is considered to be a pretty complicated technique that is squeezed into a few lines :)

All of the code follows the video below to improve your learning experience.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/UWIFtzUjDLw</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/UWIFtzUjDLw</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Programming]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Cheat Sheet is Here : http://goo.gl/OPMjte

Slower Java Tutorial : http://goo.gl/UHdlyP

How to Install Java & Eclipse : http://goo.gl/vEEEJE

Best Java Book : http://amzn.to/2l27h2h

Support Me on Patreon : https://www.patreon.com/derekbanas

In this Java programming Tutorial I'll teach you all of the core knowledge needed to write Java code in 30 minutes. This is the most popular request from everyone.

I specifically cover the following topics: primitive data types, comments, class, import, Scanner, final, Strings, static, private, protected, public, constructors, math, hasNextLine, nextLine, getters, setters, method overloading, Random, casting, toString, conversion from Strings to primitives, converting from primitives to Strings, if, else, else if, print, println, printf, logical operators, comparison operators, ternary operator, switch, for, while, break, continue, do while, polymorphism, arrays, for each, multidimensional arrays and more.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/WPvGqX-TXP0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/WPvGqX-TXP0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 53]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get everything here: http://goo.gl/4kePr

I first started the how to make Java games series to solve a bunch of problems. Many people in the forums are posting extremely complicated ways to rotate polygons in Java for example. It is very easy to rotate polygons!

I also saw many people struggle with other calculations like: 

1. Finding the length and angle of a line between vectors 
2. Calculate the points of a rotating polygon 
3. Calculate the area of irregular polygons 
4. Find the center points of an irregular polygon 
5. Repeat keyboard clicks if the user holds down a key

Much, much more....]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/fK0fxjbjdQA</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/fK0fxjbjdQA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 52]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the Code: http://goo.gl/JfZla

In this part of my Java video tutorial, I create the spaceship object and a keyboard listener. I will use the keyboard listener to move the ship around the screen.

It is so easy to randomly add objects to the game we started making here Make a Java Video Game. I slowed things down a bit here, just to make sure you completely get the process.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/lebZd9bDnc8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/lebZd9bDnc8</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 59]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the game code: http://goo.gl/OKMBp

In the last part of this tutorial I showed you how to make the PhotonTorpedo class using a UML class diagram.

In this tutorial, I show you how to make your space ship shoot the torpedos on the screen. As you'll see, because I used good OOP design principles in the last video, adding the shooting feature will require very few changes.

All of the code above is heavily commented to help you learn.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/ptsNLcQYxCQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/ptsNLcQYxCQ</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 51]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Game code is here: http://goo.gl/M0Tqj

Here I continue what I started in Make a Java Video Game. If you haven't seen it, watch it before this video.

I'll now create the GameBoard class that will animate all of my asteroids. I redraw the board using threads. If you are rusty on them, check out my Java Thread Video Tutorial.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/sSbcAFqpw-o</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/sSbcAFqpw-o</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Install Eclipse for Java]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get the Steps in List Format: http://goo.gl/Lrq67

I've been asked to show you how to Install Eclipse for Java a few times lately. So in this video I'll show you how to install Eclipse step-by-step.

Not only will I show you how to install eclipse, but I'll also cover how to install Java, set up code completion and install java libraries.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/svJQu6LUSTs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/svJQu6LUSTs</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 55]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Everything from the video: http://goo.gl/aXpXa

In this part of my Java video tutorial I focus on Java OOP Design Principles. We are still making the game we started , but now I'm creating all of the needed parts with strong use of encapsulation.

I walk you through the think process of going from features needed to a finished UML class diagram. I know this is an odd way to talk about OOP design principles, but I wanted to present it in a new fresh way.

What's better than making a game while learning OOP?]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/upmRIZwAHAY</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/upmRIZwAHAY</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:36:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sabermetrics 2]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Get Everything: http://goo.gl/QI8dG

I continue my Sabermetrics Baseball tutorial. I'm going to introduce a few new SQL functions being CONCAT, COALESCE and HAVING.

We will also calculate the top players based on RBIs, HRs, Batting Average, On Base Percentage, and Slugging Percentage. And, I'll show you how to pull in data on the players position and their salary.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/02HlbJ18aYc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/02HlbJ18aYc</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 5]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Code is Here: http://wp.me/p1U2FZ-1vY

Best Java Book : http://goo.gl/FtKp0m

Here I continue my Java Video Tutorial by covering methods, or functions in Java.

I spend a considerable amount of time on those things that tend to confuse people who are learning Java. I review how class variables differ from local variables and provide numerous examples of methods.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/1HTsLK_m2ao</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/1HTsLK_m2ao</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 15]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Code is Here: http://goo.gl/8I3sW

Best Java Book : http://goo.gl/FtKp0m

In this part of the Java Video Tutorial I cover interfaces, abstract classes, abstract methods and more.

You need interfaces and abstract classes because Java doesn't allow you to inherit from more than one other class. You would use an interface when you want to force the user of the interface to create every method in the interface.

You use an abstract method when you need some flexibility.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/1PPDoAKbaNA</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/1PPDoAKbaNA</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Java Video Tutorial 20]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Code Here: http://goo.gl/THKae

Best Java Book : http://goo.gl/FtKp0m

I introduce you to Graphical User Interfaces (GUI) in this part of my Java Video Tutorial. I focus specifically on Java Swing and its components.

We figure out how to display frames, panels, labels, buttons, text areas and more. I also go over the Dimension object and the Java Toolkit, which allows you to ask questions of the operating system.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/3XB3in9Xqy8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/3XB3in9Xqy8</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 01:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>