<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[DevTube the place where developer videos live]]></description>
        <link>https://dev.tube</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 19:00:51 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://dev.tube/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Future of Event-driven Microservices with Spring Cloud Stream - Kenny Bastani @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

When you’re building microservices, managing state becomes a distributed systems problem. Instead of being able to manage state as transactions inside the boundaries of a single monolithic application, a microservice must be able to manage consistency by using transactions that are distributed across a network of many different applications and databases.

Event-driven architectures are a key component of solving data consistency issues in microservices. This session explores the problems of data consistency in microservices and the various event-driven practices that include CQRS and Event Sourcing. We will look at how these popular practices are implemented using Spring Boot and Spring Cloud Stream.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/0C7J7hFv_pk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/0C7J7hFv_pk</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RAML - Specification to manage the API lifecycle - Fátima Casaú @ Spring I/O 2016]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2016 - 19 -20 May Barcelona

RESTful API Modeling Language (RAML), is a specification that looks like YAML and makes easy to manage the API lifecycle. In short, in this talk, I show the features of RAML and how to integrate in a Spring Boot project]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/1AlLiBfylh8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/1AlLiBfylh8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[DDD Strategic Design with Spring Boot - Michael Plöd @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

Slides: https://speakerdeck.com/mploed/ddd-strategic-design-with-spring-boot-examples

One of the most precious parts of Domain Driven Design are the concepts of Strategic Design. These concepts include the Bounded Context, the Context Map and the patterns that are being documented in the Context Map.

This talk explains all of the topics mentioned above as well as practical usage scenarios such as migrating a monolithic landscape to Microservices. In order to get hands-on I will also demonstrate the concepts surrounding Strategic Design with an application landscape of various Spring Boot Applications.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/2hMf5EwNOWE</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/2hMf5EwNOWE</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Database centric applications with Spring Boot and jOOQ - Michael Simons @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

GitHub repo: https://github.com/michael-simons/bootiful-databases

jOOQ is one of several quite different technologies to access relational data from Java based applications.

jOOQ is short for "Java object oriented querying" and describes a query builder framework that takes a look at your database schema, independent wether you use an Open Source database like PostgreSQL or an commercial product like Oracle Database., and provides you with a domain specific language (DSL) for generating statements.

jOOQs goal is explicitly not to shield the user from SQL but providing a type safe way to use it.

Learn in this session who you can facilitate the "magic" of Spring Boot to provide jOOQ with needed resources and then use it to publish advanced analytic queries as HTTP apis.

Along the way you learn how automatic database migrations help you to do continuous delivery even with database centric applications.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/4pwTd6NEuN0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/4pwTd6NEuN0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KEYNOTE - From Spring Framework 4.3 to 5.0 - Juergen Hoeller, Stéphane Nicoll and Phil Webb]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Spring team is currently working towards not one but two new generations of the framework: 4.3, scheduled for GA at the end of May... and 5.0, scheduled for early 2017. This keynote presents Spring Framework 4.3 with a focus on its developer experience, featuring live demos with the closely aligned Spring Boot 1.4. In the second part, we'll be introducing the infrastructure themes for next year's Spring Framework 5.0: JDK 9, HTTP/2, and reactive architectures.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/4svNgwAJyK0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/4svNgwAJyK0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Architecture Deep Dive in Spring Security - Joe Grandja @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

This talk will provide an Architectural Overview of Spring Security with a focus on Authentication and Authorization. The main goal is to empower users with a deeper knowledge of how Spring Security works “under the covers”. This talk will also demo various Authentication and Authorization scenarios.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/8rnOsF3RVQc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/8rnOsF3RVQc</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KEYNOTE - Designing Applications: The Reactive Way - Rossen Stoyanchev and Stephane Maldini]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2016 - 19 -20 May Barcelona

Over the past year the Spring Framework and Reactor teams have been busy working on support for reactive programming models. Reactor 2.5 is in milestone phases with great momentum behind it. Spring Framework 5 M1 is just around the corner. In this keynote we'll take on you a journey to help you understand the major paradigm shift that's taking place and what it means for the way we write and scale applications.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/APk2dMdXqzI</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/APk2dMdXqzI</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Spring ecosystem in 50 minutes - Jeroen Sterken @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

Slides: https://www.slideshare.net/JeroenSterken1/the-spring-ecosystem-in-50-min

There are currently over 20 main projects, most of them containing multiple subprojects. Do you know each one of them? Probably not.

In this session we have only 1 main goal, taking a bird’s-eye view on all of them. I know, this will get challenging, but afterwards you’ll hopefully discover those projects that you never thought existed. Let’s dive in!]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/AnTViprbdp0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/AnTViprbdp0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Extending Spring Data - Petar Tahchiev @ Spring I/O 2016]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2016 - 19 -20 May Barcelona

This talk will focus on some particular features of spring-data. It will outline the problems we had to overcome while building the administrative interface for the nemesis e-commerce platform. Our administrative interface is a javascript application that talks to our spring-data-rest enabled platform. We will cover topics like, JPA alternative domain types, querydsl, projections and json schema.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/Ar8WIcD7pz4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/Ar8WIcD7pz4</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Data Processing With Microservices - Michael Minella @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

GitHub repo: https://github.com/mminella/data-microservices

When the word “microservice” comes up, many thoughts go directly to REST endpoints powering websites. However, applying the 12 factor concepts to batch and integration style workloads can provide immense benefits. In this talk, we will walk through creating data microservices for both streaming applications (integration) via Spring Cloud Stream as well as short lived microservices via Spring Cloud Task. We’ll finish by looking at how Spring Cloud DataFlow can be used to orchestrate these microservices into useful applications. A general knowledge of Spring and Spring Boot will be useful for this talk.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/COzkPkHZMG8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/COzkPkHZMG8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud-native streaming and event-driven microservices - Marius Bogoevici @ Spring I/O 2016]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2016 - 19 -20 May Barcelona

The future of scalable data processing is event-driven microservices! They provide a powerful paradigm that solves issues typically associated with distributed applications, such as availability, data consistency, or communication complexity, and allows the creation of sophisticated and extensible data processing pipelines, bridging the gap between the big data and more traditional enterprise integration world.

Building on the ease of development and deployment provided by Spring Boot, the cloud native capabilities of Spring Cloud, and the messaging model and integration patterns of Spring Integration, the Spring Cloud Stream project provides a simple and powerful framework for event-driven microservices. It defines primitives and abstractions specifically addressing the needs of both event-driven integration, as well as data streaming. For addressing the complexity of deployment, at a higher level of abstraction, Spring Cloud Data Flow is an integrated orchestration layer that provides a highly productive experience for deploying and managing sophisticated data pipelines consisting of standalone microservices. A pluggable runtime SPI allows Spring Cloud Data Flow to coordinate these applications across a variety of distributed runtime platforms such as Apache YARN, Cloud Foundry, Kubernetes, or Apache Mesos. We will demonstrate how to easily create complex data processing pipelines that bridge the world of big data and enterprise integration together, by building Spring Cloud Stream applications from the ground up, and, in the end, how to orchestrate them with Spring Cloud Data Flow.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/FT9_WR4i28o</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/FT9_WR4i28o</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Testing for Unicorns - Alex Soto @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

Slides: https://www.slideshare.net/asotobu/testing-for-unicorns-77069262

One of the most important benefits of automated testing is to ensure a fast and safe code refactoring to evolve our system architecture. The main problem is how to write tests that are easy to write, easy to follow and not time consuming during development nor execution time.

In this session, we are going to explore some powerful Java testing libraries that will help you write better (unit) tests focusing on the main Unicorns architecture challenges such as validating microservices endpoints, remote calls to other microservices or just asynchronous/reactive code.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/GpQ1Nwyimkg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/GpQ1Nwyimkg</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Front Ends for Back End Developers - Matt Raible @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

Slides: https://www.slideshare.net/mraible/front-ends-for-back-end-developers-spring-io-2017

Are you a backend developer that’s being pushed into front end development? Are you frustrated with all JavaScript frameworks and build tools you have to learn to be a good UI developer? If so, this session is for you! We’ll explore the tools of the trade for fronted development (npm, yarn, Gulp, Webpack, Yeoman) and learn the basics of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. We’ll dive into the intricacies of Bootstrap, Material Design, ES6, and TypeScript. Finally, after getting you up to speed with all this new tech, we’ll show how it can all be found and integrated through the fine and dandy JHipster project.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/HnX09pdxEQI</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/HnX09pdxEQI</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Container orchestration on Apache Mesos - DC/OS for Spring Boot devs - Johannes Unterstein]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

Slides: https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1tRWUJnGCGMbYjB11koaOukgzD-zNB8MaimeoFPJ2_JQ/edit

In the era of Docker, big data and microservices it is really important to distribute your applications reasonable across your cluster and keep a good overview of all of your running applications. Because of this, cluster management software like Apache Mesos and DC/OS are very important and popular. In this session we will implement a java based service using spring boot and will start him locally and with docker-compose. Then we will deploy our service to DC/OS and see how easy it is to scale, upgrade, monitor and do other fancy stuff. And the best thing for the demo: We will have a nice UI and super cool CLI.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/JM_WcsUN5fs</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/JM_WcsUN5fs</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Awesome Tools to Level Up Your Spring Cloud Architecture - Andreas Evers @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

Slides: https://speakerdeck.com/andreasevers/awesome-tools-to-level-up-your-spring-cloud-architecture-1

Getting up and running with Spring Cloud is a breeze. But once the initial setup is done, it needs to be complemented with an ecosystem that can cope with the extra operational complexity and quality concerns. While running Spring Cloud in production for years, we have integrated some interesting tools for documentation, operations and testing.

During this talk you will see a demo of an integrated platform based on Spring Cloud, including tools like Spring Cloud Contract, wiremock, saboteur, ELK, Spinnaker, Spring Boot Admin and more. One of these tools is a dashboard for visualising Spring Cloud microservice architecture, which has recently been open sourced.

Documenting, testing, troubleshooting, and monitoring highly distributed systems in microservice architectures is hard. Finding quality, complementary tools in the wilds of open source can be even harder. Join this talk for a pragmatic look at taming some of the challenges of running microservices in production.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/JzgBkodsFsM</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/JzgBkodsFsM</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Experiences from using discovery services in a microservice landscape - Magnus Larsson @ Spring I/O]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

One of the most important components in a microservice landscape is the discovery service. During the last few years a large number of alternatives for service discovery have evolved, specifically in the area of container infrastructures.

This presentation will, based on my experiences, go through some of the alternatives. The presentation will cover discovery service components in Netflix OSS, Docker Swarm, Amazon ECS and Google Kubernetes. We will also cover how to use Spring Cloud to write microservices that are independent of the selected discovery service, i.e. that can be used with any of the alternatives without requiring modifications of the code.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/LkIOSKd5zew</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/LkIOSKd5zew</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[40 Tips & Tricks for Spring in IntelliJ IDEA -  Yann Cébron & Stéphane Nicoll @ Spring I/O 2016]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2016 - 19 -20 May Barcelona

IDEs can be powerful, but hard to learn. Some features are hidden or simply not well known.

Let’s end this dilemma and make you more productive and efficient when working on Spring applications.
Learn how to navigate, edit and perform refactorings across a variety of common Spring technologies.  

You’ll leave this session with a whole stack of power tricks - right from the developers working on it.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/OfdERvmIJXc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/OfdERvmIJXc</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Spring Boot and Cloud for Legacy Applications - Marten Deinum @ Spring I/O 2016]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2016 - 19 -20 May Barcelona

Spring Boot as well as the Spring Cloud projects are very neat and powerful technologies. But how easy are they to apply to existing application and how can they help improve existing applications.

In this talk we will take a look at a legacy application and introduce Spring Boot and some of the Spring Cloud technologies to it.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/Q_WIvCsY6G0</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/Q_WIvCsY6G0</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Cloud Native Java - Josh Long @ Spring I/O 2016]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2016 - 19 -20 May Barcelona

"It is not necessary to change. Survival is not mandatory." -W. Edwards Deming

Work takes time to flow through an organization and ultimately be deployed to production where it captures value. It’s critical to reduce time-to-production. Software - for many organizations and industries - is a competitive advantage.

Organizations break their larger software ambitions into smaller, independently deployable, feature -centric batches of work - microservices. In order to reduce the round-trip between stations of work, organizations collapse or consolidate as much of them as possible and automate the rest; developers and operations beget “devops,” cloud-based services and platforms (like Cloud Foundry) automate operations work and break down the need for ITIL tickets and change management boards.

But velocity, for velocity’s sake, is dangerous. Microservices invite architectural complexity that few are prepared to address. In this talk, we’ll look at how high performance organizations like Ticketmaster, Alibaba, and Netflix make short work of that complexity with Spring Boot and Spring Cloud.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/R4s4z7fTEH4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/R4s4z7fTEH4</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Deep Learning with DeepLearning4J and Spring Boot - Artur Garcia & Dimas Cabré @ Spring I/O 2017]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Spring I/O 2017 - 18 -19 May, Barcelona

We'll start with a review on recent advances in Deep Learning. Then we'll present DeepLearning4J (the first commercial-grade, open-source, distributed deep-learning library written for Java) and explore how it covers topics explained in the initial review. We'll then present a Spring Boot application with some functionality run by a Neural Network. Finally we'll explore the possibilities of implementing a Supervised Learning System using Spring Boot Actuator, which will lead to a trained monitoring system that can be interacted with actuator endpoints.]]></description>
            <link>https://dev.tube/video/RlL9MNT-R3k</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://dev.tube/video/RlL9MNT-R3k</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 01:34:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>